Inventory of the International Association for the Evaluation of Educational Achievement Records, 1959-1992
Hoover Institution Archives
- Curriculum Theory Network, No 6, Winter 1970-1971 (Box 310)
- Collection: Civic Education, pretest, attitudes scales and progress reports 1970s (Box 311)
- Civic Education Affective Domain, 1969 (Box 312)
- Civic Education (Box 312)
- Civic Education, pretest (Box 312)
- Science Pre test (Box 313)
- Collection of documents: IEA Bureau Meeting (Box 314)
- Collection of documents and Various proposals, from 1970s (Box 315)
- Six-subject study, national options, stage 2 (Box 316)
- Collection of letters 1968 and more (Box 316)
- Six-subject study, national options, stage 2, by countries (Box 317)
- Six-subject study sampling, by country 1970-1971 (Box 318)
- Six-subject study, dry run manual (Box 318)
- Six-subject study, data bank (Box 318)
- Six-subject study scoring tests, stage 2 (Box 319)
- Sampling, stage 3 and correspondence (Box 319)
- Sampling, stage 3 and correspondence (Box 319)
- Documents (Box 320)
- NCSQ binder (full copy) (Box 321)
- NCSQ, National Centers comments, Iran - USA (Stage 2 1971) (Box 321)
- NCSQ, Replies to IEA/NCSQ/5, (Stage 3 1971), Belgium FR - USA (Box 321)
- Data Management (label Sweden), ICC 1992 (Box 322)
- Computer report: IEA Six-subjects Data Bank Manual, circa 1975 (Box 322)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Scotland (Box 323)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Ireland (Box 323)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Ireland (civic education booklet) (Box 323)
- Collection of documents 1970s - 1980s (invoices, letters from Roy Philips) (Box 323)
- Accounting reports and procedures 1968 - 1972 (Box 323)
- Binder with papers (Box 323)
- IEA memorandum and grant proposal 1970s; UNESCO - reading study, Motivation study, Van-Leer Foundation (Box 324)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Scotland (stage 3) (Box 324)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Japan (stage 3) (Box 324)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Scotland (stage 3) more booklets (Box 324)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Israel (civic education) documents, non-English, circa 1971 (Box 325)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Sweden (stage 3) (Box 325)
- PREF INST - 1973, non-English (Box 326)
- IEA Main testing, Sweden, Stage 3, 1971 (Box 326)
- IEA Bureau Meeting, May 27-28 1971 Professor Husen (Stockholm) (Box 326)
- Document: Proposition 1975:9 Reforming?? Sweden. Stockholm University (Box 327)
- Publication: European Council 1973 [Politics in Educational Research across Europe. Document in French] (Box 327)
- Document: IEA National Case Study Questionnaire Israel, December 1963 (Box 327)
- IEA England - revised draft [seems like booklets from the Six-subject Study] (Box 327)
- Various documents including IEA Bureau Meeting, Frankfurt 1972 (Box 328)
- IEA Science Tests, November 1969 [Husen] (Box 328)
- Documents from the International Institution for Pedagogy at University of Stockholm, 1986 (Box 328)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Sweden (stage 3) more booklets (Box 328)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Israel (stage 3) (Box 328)
- SAMBAND Med Main Testing 1970 (Box 329)
- Binder with tips and comments for discussion on the Future of the IEA - Friday morning (Box 329)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population, teachers' literature (Box 329)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population, teachers' literature (Box 329)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population, teachers' science (Box 329)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population, teachers' English (Box 329)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population. French and others (Box 330)
- Maps of questions and items by country and population. Civics and others (Box 331)
- KONTOUTDRAG, 1-6/1985 (Box 332)
- IEA 2nd Math Study, correspondence until 7/1976 (Box 332)
- KONTOUTDRAG, 7/1984 - 12/1984 (Box 333)
- Questionnaire from Chile (Box 333)
- IEA Bureau meeting 1971 (Box 333)
- Six Subject Project review committee meeting 1-2/9/1971. Professor T. Husen (Box 333)
- IEA 2nd Math Study, correspondence binder 7/1980 - 7/1981 (Box 334)
- IEA 2nd Math Study, correspondence binder 5/1977 - 12/1978 (Box 334)
- IEA 2nd Math Survey, 8/1976 - 4/1977 [paper about why US should participate] (Box 335)
- Research Fellows correspondence, 1983? (Box 336)
- Conference materials, Sweden 1989 (Box 337)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments India (Box 338)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Italy and Thailand (Box 338)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments India (stage 2) more booklets (Box 338)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Thailand (stage 2) more booklets (Box 338)
- Publication: IEA, Phase II, stage 2, Science, December 1968 (pink cover, c/o UNESCO Hamburg) (Box 338)
- NCSQ, comments: Australia - India, Stage 2 (Box 339)
- NCSQ, correspondence 1971 - 1972 (Box 339)
- NCSQ, comments: New-Zealand - USA (Box 339)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Chile (Box 340)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Chile [Science?] (Box 340)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Italy (Box 340)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Italy (Box 340)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Italy (Box 340)
- IEA Six-subject survey national instruments and manuals - Italy [Science?] (Box 340)
- Drafts of French as a Foreign Language (Box 341)
- Drafts of the National Case Study: an empirical comparative study of 21 education system (Box 341)
- English as Foreign Language (Box 342)
- Final Publication - NCSQ National Profile (Box 342)
- IEA General Volume, correspondence with Phillips, Anderson and others. Mid 1970s (Box 343)
- NCSQ National Profiles, Roy Phillips 1973-4 (Box 343)
- Final Publication, general volume, comments and correspondence (Box 343)
- Publications: NAVF ARSMELDING 1964, INTEGRALCHNUNG and others (Box 344)
- Information "kit" in German (Box 344)
- Drafts of Technical Report, 1973 (Box 344)
- Drafts of Technical Report, Vol. II, 1974 (Box 344)
- Collection of documents, not in English (maybe German) (Box 345)
- Second Study of Mathematics - Bulletin #5, Nov 1980 and other correspondence about it (Box 345)
- Letters from accountants 1986 ERNST and WHINNEY AB (Box 346)
- Collection of tests and instruments (Box 346)
- IEA DATA BANK BULLETIN (Six Subject Study) (Box 346)
- Collection of documents about test scoring and scale (1971) (Box 347)
- IEA Newsletter (Box 347)
- IEA Pre-School Education Committee 1972 (Box 348)
- IEA Six Subject Committee 1971, TNP (Box 348)
- Envelope with coding materials (Box 348)
- manuscript "Teaching Behaviors and Student Achievement" 1970 (Box 348)
- Correspondence 1970s (Box 348)
- Collection: the civic education curriculum and he measurement of its cognitive outcomes in different nations (Box 349)
- Cards with contacts information (Box 349)
- IEA Annotated Bibliography. 1979 (Box 349)
- Collection of documents from 1969 (Box 350)
- IEA Phase II Stage 2, Science, Dec 1968 (2 copies) (Box 350)
- Publications of the Center For The Study Of Evaluation Of Instructional Programs. UCLA 1968. Comments on Bloom's paper entitled "toward a theory of testing which includes measurement - evaluation - assessment" (Box 350)
- Publication: INTERACTION, A science unit for the Primary Grades SCIS-S (Box 350)
- Publication: Changing Culture [seems to be used in US schools] (Box 350)
- Publication: Language and communication (Box 350)
- IEA English as a Foreign Language 1970 - Master copies of tests (Box 351)
- Package in unknown language 1975, Robert Hoghielm (Box 351)
- IEA - International Project on the Evaluation of Educational Achievements, April 1964. UNESCO. Bulleting #4 (Box 352)
- IEA - International Association on the Evaluation of Educational Achievements, December 1968. UNESCO. Phase II, Stage 2. Manuals for national centers, school coordinators, team administrators. 2 copies (Box 352)
- IEA - International Association on the Evaluation of Educational Achievements, December 1968. UNESCO. Phase II, Stage 2. Word Knowledge (Box 352)
- IEA - International Association on the Evaluation of Educational Achievements, December 1968. UNESCO. Phase II, Stage 2. French and English as Foreign Languages, Civic Education, Scales (Box 352)
- IEA - International Association on the Evaluation of Educational Achievements, June 1970. UNESCO. Phase II, Stage 3. French as Foreign Languages (Box 352)
- Cross-National Study of Educational Attainment - Final Report on the six subject study. 1969 (Box 352)
- IEA manual 3 for test administrators, stage 3 (Box 353)
- IEA manuals, Sweden, not sure what study (Box 353)
- IEA questionnaires for attitude and descriptive scales, September 1970 (Box 353)
- Invoices and various documents (Box 353)
- Publication: IEA (project) Item statistics by country and target population, Phase I: International Study of Achievement in Mathematics A comparison of Twelve Countries. (Box 354)
- Technical Volume, Roy Phillips, early drafts and correspondence 1971 (Box 355)
- ESL report, correspondence Vol. 4, 1971 - (Box 356)
- ESL report, Vol. 2, Roy Phillips (Box 356)
- IEA correspondence 1967-1969 (Box 357)
- IEA correspondence 1967-1969 [seems like this is Husen's files] (Box 357)
- Few envelopes with small white computer cards (Box 358)
- Invoices and accounting (Box 358)
- Collection of Word Knowledge instruments (Box 358)
- IEA correspondence, early 1970s including memorandum on press conference for science, literature and reading projects (Box 359)
- Finish sample, stage 3 (Box 359)
- Auditing and Accounting 1969 - 1970 (Box 360)
- Publication: The Bank of Sweden Fund (Box 361)
- Accounting and Invoices, early 1970s (Box 361)
- Accounting and Salaries, early 1970s (Box 361)
- IEA International Press Conference - 24 May 1973 (Box 362)
- Data Files, stage 1+ 2 (Box 362)
- Data Bank, Dirty Data File, Stage 3 (Box 362)
- Data Log, early 1970s (Box 362)
- Attitudes and Descriptive Scales (Box 363)
- General Attitudes and Descriptive Scales (Box 363)
- Data Processing meetings, Roy Phillips 1970s (Box 364)
- Data Bank correspondence file, inside IEA 1970s (Box 364)
- Correction, Additions and Checks, mid 1970s (Box 365)
- Data Bank (Box 365)
- Data Processing Stockholm 1970 - 1973, invoices (Box 366)
- Data Archives, Jack's Binder (??) (Box 366)
- Binders with list (students?) and grades in different subjects. [seems like sample information for different schools and classes] (Box 367)
- Binders with list (students?) and large maps and tables (Box 368)
- Binders with computer printouts and path-analysis diagrams (??) (Box 369)
- IEA Scales and IEA Data Bank - 1970s (Box 370)
- IEA Data Bank, program freezer (computer printouts) (Box 370)
- File documents and other data processing in New York. Weights. 1972 (Box 371)
- Letters and correspondence with different countries. 1969-1966 (Box 371)
- Topics and Discussion on accuracy, missing, pilots and tryout and civic pretest, 1972-1973 (Box 372)
- Civic Study: scoring key and pretests forms, documents and reports from different countries (Box 373)
- Science: tests (Box 373)
- civic education national versions from Australia, England, USA and Chile (Box 373)
- Reviews with sub-folder for IEA members and non-IEA members (Box 373)
- Computer printouts 1975 (Box 374)
- Computer printouts 1981 (Box 375)
- Collection of publications, documents and text from Sweden (1954/1955) and bulletins and articles from the 1980s (Box 376)
- Collection of publications (Box 377)
- USA media clips about SES /Race (Box 377)
- Educational Statistics Japan 1976 (Blue Booklet) + IEA Tokyo meeting 1978 (Box 378)
- Harvard Conferences 1973 - Travel and Accommodations (Box 378)
- Collection of documents from 1985, including letters on cooperation between IEA and ACER (Box 379)
- Collection of IEA Civic Study Instruments (non-English) (Box 380)
- IEA memorandum 1971/1972 (Box 380)
- IEA ESL Tests, March 1970 (Box 380)
- IEA primary reading proposals 1973 (Box 380)
- IEA Bureau Meeting binder, Stockholm 1971 (Box 381)
- Publication: A study of educational opportunities to women in Sri-Lanka. Date unknown (Box 382)
- Cooperative Math Tests ETS, 1962 (Box 382)
- Miscellaneous 1971, including letter and document from Chile (Box 382)
- IEA Bulletin #4, May 1964 (Box 383)
- Collection of booklets, instruments and tests [seems to be Pilot or FIMS] (Box 393)
- IEA Manual for National Centers (S42/6) (Box 384)
- IEA Manual for School Testing Organizers (S42/7} (Box 384)
- IEA Manual for Administrators (S42/8) (Box 384)
- Tests and questionnaires: Science, 1964. Syllabus and curriculum from Israel and Australia (Box 385)
- Computer printouts 1984, Sweden (Box 386)
- Computer printouts 1984, Sweden (Box 386)
- Computer printouts 1984, Sweden (Box 386)
- Contents of Stage 2 Instruments binder (Box 386)
- IEA Phase II Stage 2, Science including tests on understanding the nature of science, Nov 1969 (Box 386)
- IEA Phase II Stage 2, Science including tests on understanding the nature of science, Nov 1969 (Box 386)
- Report (Box 386)
- Collection of publications (Box 387)
- IEA GA minutes 1987 (Box 387)
- Semi-annual report, 1988. IEA GA minutes 1987 NYC and report about "Teaching and Learning Social Values and Morality" (Box 388)
- IEA GA minutes 1987, attachments about SISS (Box 388)
- IEA GA minutes 1986 (Box 388)
- IEA GA minutes 1986 (Box 388)
- Publication: IEA Pre School Education Survey (Belgium) (Box 388)
- Collection: IEA GA minutes Tokyo 1978 (Box 389)
- IEA GA minutes China 1990 (Box 389)
- Collection: IEA GA minutes Seoul, Korea 1989 (Box 389)
- IEA 1987 (Box 389)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1979 (Box 390)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1979, IEA GA meeting minutes 1979 and related documents (Box 390)
- Educational Studies in Mathematics, 6, 127-186, copy of paper (Box 390)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1974 [seems like the IEA leadership of that day were central in the field of educational research and development] (Box 390)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1971 (Box 390)
- Australian and England documents on syllabuses and exams (Box 390)
- National Case Study Questionnaire from different countries, early 1970s (Box 391)
- Miscellaneous (non-English), 1977 (Box 392)
- Miscellaneous (non-English), 1973 (Box 392)
- Reprints of papers by Eve Malmquist (Box 392)
- Curriculum and text books from different countries (Box 392)
- IEA Data Bank Bulletin #4, September 1975 (Box 393)
- Codebooks for different countries (Box 393)
- Instrument for Science study 1970 (Box 393)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments Belgium Flemish (Box 394)
- Large tables and maps with statistics (Box 394)
- IEA International Science Committee (Box 395)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments (Box 395)
- Tables and Coding sheets (Box 396)
- Reports from national centers on testing phase 2, 1970 (Thailand, New-Zealand) (Box 396)
- IEA Council Meeting, Berlin 1975 (Box 396)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1973 (Box 396)
- Miscellaneous correspondence early 1970s (Box 396)
- Reports from national centers on testing phase 2, 1971 (Box 397)
- Proposals for Data Analysis and Data Bank (Box 397)
- Publication: IEA Phase II, Stage 2: FSL, ESL, CIVIC, Attitudes and Descriptive Scales (1969) (Box 397)
- Correspondence 1965 (Box 398)
- Correspondence 1964 (Box 398)
- IEA Manuals 1969 (Box 398)
- IEA questionnaires for attitude and descriptive scales, September 1970 (Box 398)
- Correspondence 1969 - 1972 (Box 399)
- Correspondence 1969 - 1972 (Box 399)
- Correspondence 1969 - 1973 (Box 399)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments France (Box 399)
- Day File, February 1972 (Box 400)
- Day File, March 1972 (Box 400)
- Day File, April 1971 (Box 401)
- Day File, May-July 1971 (Box 401)
- Day File, February - March 1971 (Box 402)
- Day File, August - December 1970 (Box 402)
- Day File, December 1970 - January 1971 (Box 403)
- Accounting and budget (Box 403)
- Accounting and budget, alternative costs (Box 403)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1971 (Box 403)
- Miscellaneous correspondence 1968 - 1970 (Box 403)
- IEA monographs series (Box 404)
- IEA monographs series (Box 404)
- Technical Report manuscript (Box 404)
- Binder: IEA Tape Information (Box 405)
- Binder: IEA Mathematics Codebook I 1979 (Box 405)
- Accounting (Box 405)
- Computer printouts (Box 405)
- Day File, December 1972 (Box 406)
- Day File, April 1973 (Box 406)
- Day File, August 1972 (Box 406)
- Day File, November 1972 (Box 407)
- Day File, July 1972 (Box 407)
- Day File, 1973 (Box 407)
- Day File, February 1973 (Box 407)
- Day File, December 1972 (Box 408)
- Day File, April 1973 (Box 408)
- Day File, August 1972 (Box 408)
- Day File, April 1972 (Box 409)
- Day File, May 1972 (Box 409)
- Day File, June 1972 (Box 409)
- Negatives, French as a foreign language (Box 410)
- France and Scotland (1970s) (Box 410)
- Instruments phase 3 (1970s?) (Box 411)
- Press Releaser, publication on Science, Reading and Literature (1973) (Box 411)
- Instruments stage 2 (????) (Box 412)
- KONTOUTDRAG 1-6/1986; tables and printouts, [seems to be related to budgets and finance] (Box 412)
- Mathematics Math I Codebook (Box 413)
- IEA data processing memos (Box 414)
- IEA Data Bank Manual (1970s) (Box 415)
- IEA Codebook 1 (Box 415)
- IEA Codebook 2 (Box 415)
- Financial and Legal, late 1960s (Box 416)
- IEA Code Book (Box 416)
- Office forms binder (Box 417)
- Various meeting minutes (Box 417)
- Math 2 test runs (Box 417)
- Booklets and manuals for Germany (FR) and Netherlands (Box 418)
- Day file, February 1969 - July 1969 (Box 419)
- Reading Comprehension, India (Box 419)
- Codebook for Follow Up Project 1972 (Box 420)
- National Centers report on optional data (?) (Box 420)
- Dry Run National Versions (Box 421)
- Deviations IEA/A/73, Stage 2 (Box 421)
- IEA/A/164 - A/170, 1973/1974, includes revisions of chapters, papers from Harvard conference and NCSQ (Box 422)
- Replies to IEA/A/32 Stage 3 (Box 422)
- IEA/A/187 - A/200, circa 1974 (Box 423)
- Replies to IEA/A/57 - A/62, early 1970s (Box 423)
- Math Study, phase I, notes from Japan (Box 424)
- Requests for use and copies of Test and Instruments 1974 (Box 424)
- Computer manuals: IBM and Fortran software (Box 425)
- Science coding sheet (Box 425)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments, Rumania, Stage 3 (Box 426)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments, Iran, Stage 3 (Box 426)
- Instruments, Booklet - Belgium, Chile, India, Italy (Box 427)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments, Netherlands, Stage 3 (Box 427)
- IEA Six-subjects Study National Instruments, Belgium (FR), Stage 3 (Box 428)
- IEA - ESL (??) (Box 428)
- IEA Meeting, 1971, Stockholm (Box 429)
- Collection of miscellaneous academic papers on education (Box 429)
- Science International Documents, 1968. Tests and Questionnaires (Box 430)
- IEA Documents 1963-1964 (Box 430)
- Science, population I, subtests 3 and 4. Pretests? (Box 431)
- Civic Education, 1976-1977 (Box 432)
- S42 (cont), 1967 (Box 432)
- Civic Education Monograph Final Version (Box 433)
- Civic Education Monographs and Report, Roy Phillips (Box 433)
- Civic Education, correspondence Farnen and Committee, 1973, Vol. 3 (Box 434)
- UNESCO PROV Stansinstr (Box 434)
- Collection of publications from Iran and Israel about educational statistics and research. Mid and late 1960s (Box 435)
- IEA six Subject surveys, main run, Finland. 1970s (Box 436)
- Surveys, tests and questionnaires. 1970s (Box 436)
- JCL IBM 360 (Box 437)
- Publication: IEA, Phase II, stage 2, Science, December 1968 (pink cover, c/o UNESCO Hamburg) (Box 437)
- Computer printouts (Box 437)
- IEA Bulletins 1960, 1963, 1964, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 437)
- IEA GA Meeting binder, Stockholm August 1986 (Box 438)
- UNESCO Hamburg, coding sheet and item analysis (Box 438)
- IEA Bureau Meeting, May 1971 (Box 439)
- IEA Bureau Meeting, May 1971 Stockholm (Box 439)
- ESL report binder, comments on chapters (Box 439)
- IEA Bureau meeting, 1971 Stockholm (Box 440)
- IEA English instrument, Stage 3 (Box 440)
- Finland file, 1974 (Box 440)
- Stage 3, Questionnaires Except most Civics, 1974 (Box 440)
- Stage 3, manuals, 1970 (Box 440)
- Dr. TNP IEA Bureau meeting, 1971 (Box 441)
- IEA Bureau meeting, 17-18 March 1972 (Box 441)
- IEA Bureau meeting, 30 June - 1 July. 1972, Stockholm (Box 441)
- Publication: Categorizing the IEA reading Items by ratings, factor analysis, cluster analysis and scatergram (Box 442)
- IEA Bureau meeting, 25 Oct 1970, Amsterdam (Box 443)
- IEA Manuals binder, November 1969 (Box 444)
- Tests, unknown (Box 444)
- IEA Bureau Letters, Memos and Documents, 1971-1972 (Box 445)
- Bureau meetings 1970s (Box 445)
- Software GUTS printout (Box 446)
- Tests (Box 446)
- Tests, unknown (Box 447)
- IEA Phase II Bulletin #3, Jan 1968 (Box 448)
- IEA Phase II Bulletin #2, Jan 1968 (Box 448)
- IEA Phase II Bulletin #1, Jan 1968 (Box 448)
- IEA Bulletin #4, May 1964 (Box 448)
- IEA Bulletin #3, May 1964 (Box 448)
- IEA Phase II Stage 3, French as Foreign Language, June 1970 (2 copies) (Box 448)
- The pub project + computer printout (Box 448)
- Folder with tables [maybe cases?] (Box 449)
- PUB I, not in English (Box 449)
- UNESCO (Box 449)
- Stage 3, manuals, 1970 (Box 450)
- UNESCO Svensk Correspondence (Box 450)
- Publication: IEA, Phase II, stage 3, French as Foreign Language, October 1969 (red cover, c/o UNESCO Hamburg) (Box 451)
- collection of maps with tables (Box 451)
- Lists with names [students? Sweden?] (Box 451)
- Lists with names [students? Sweden?] (Box 451)
- Dry run, national version Sweden [not sure which study] (Box 452)
- Programming data sheet (coding) (Box 453)
- Programming data sheet (coding) (Box 453)
- Large maps with tables and stats (Box 453)
- National Dry Run - Japan, Australia, Poland, Finland (Box 454)
- ESL (say English) - master copies of chapters sent to publisher (Box 454)
- IEA SISS project 1980-1981 (Box 455)
- IEA Classroom Environment Study, documents and correspondence, until May 1981 (Box 456)
- IEA Bureau meeting, New-York 1971, Huesen (Box 457)
- SVENSKA Accounting and Invoices (Box 457)
- SVENSKA Accounting and Invoices 1972 (Box 458)
- Miscellaneous, unknown (OPL) (Box 458)
- Computer printout (Box 458)
- Correspondence (Box 459)
- Collection of documents related to the Six-subject study, 1969 (Box 460)
- IEA Bulletins 1963, 1966, 1967 (Box 461)
- Tests, part in English (reading) and part in unknown language (Box 461)
- Reports from Turkey (1964) and from other places (Box 462)
- Tests and questionnaires (Box 462)
- Reports from Sweden, early 1960s (Box 463)
- AERA, copies of Educational Researcher 1968-1971 (Box 463)
- Tests and questionnaires (Box 463)
- Manuel for OSIRIS III - Summary of control cards (Box 464)
- Civic Education, pop I (Box 465)
- French tests original (Box 466)
- Civic Education, pop I (Box 466)
- English as Foreign Language Speaking Test Tapes from Chile (Box 467)
- Tapes, small and large 1969 (Box 468)
- Variables in the between student correlation. Stage 2, 1972 (Box 469)
- Variables in the between student correlation. Stage 3, 1972 (Box 469)
- Variables in the between student correlation. Stage 2, 1972 (Box 469)
- SIMS Data book (3) (Box 469)
- Tests and questionnaires - 1970 (Box 469)
- Sweden - sampling, stage 2 (Box 469)
- IEA Six-subject Study, Data Bank Manuals, unique instruments for science (Box 470)
- IEA Six-subject Study (Box 471)
- Plastic bag: IEA Data Bank, mailing list 1979sh (Box 472)
- Miscellaneous IEA materials "not sorted" circa 1984 (Box 472)
- IEA Six-subject Study (Box 473)
- IEA Pre-Primary Project, proposal, December 1982 (Box 473)
- Miscellaneous IEA materials "not sorted": Minutes from GA meeting 1983, 1984, 1985 (Box 474)